# Vitor da Costa Domith

Juiz de Fora, Brazil | LinkedIn | GitHub

**Projects:** 

Some of the projects I've worked on in the span of the last year, made during my learning/education process, with the main focus being the learning process, as was the app's usability and design:



SCSS. HLJS and code-input template element to display

highlighted code. It uses git branches as a dynamic database with LocalStorage as a buffer to rate-limit.





A web-app developed to help and facilitate the creation of prices of produts in a business, generating all prices tables automatically. All in a practical and clear user experience.

Web-app built with React using NextJs, Scss Modules, Framer Motion, react-spring, keeping deps. low as a learning experience. Supabase as both my database and auth services. Webhooks and api Routes to handle dynamic page revalidation.

#### Tools I Use:

Functional and OOP with JavaScript and Typescript, Scss, React, react-router, react-spring, Framer Motion, NextJs, Nodels, supabase, sql, webhook, functional and oop with python, pandas, numPy, vercel, docker.

# **Work Experience:**

### **Domith Gift Stores - Retail and Wholesale:** Assitant in Management and Online Sales:

Juiz de Fora, Brazil 02/2023 - present

 Assistance in managing a team of ten co-wokers includin sales, cashiers, invoicing, shipment and stock. Handling payroll, ordering and registering products in the firm's own IMS. Fulfilling, packing and shipping online orders. Developing 'floe' to help in the decision making process of assigning prices to products both for retail and wholesale.

## Marcella Peixoto's Architecture & Interior Design Firm **Junior in-house Architect:**

Juiz de Fora, Brazil 10/2021 - 12/2022

 Alongside a team of one other junior architect and a senior architect and four interns, led the design from concept to execution for 5 projects at a time and 20 in total, with focus on structural architeture and managing structural, electrical and hydraulic/sanitary projects with partenered Engineering firms. Assisting in the allocation of resources depending on projects deadlines and leading and teaching interns best practices, Handling clients needs and demands, working with engineering firms to keep all projects compatible.

### Luana Alvarenga's Architecture & Interior Design Firm **Junior in-house Architect:**

Juiz de Fora, Brazil

07/2020 - 09/2021

 Helped leading a team of 2 interns in developing, designing and drawing plans and schemes for multiple cliens ranging from personal homes and commercial spaces to the continuous development of a school project in conjunction with a firm from São Paulo, Keeping projects in schedule and in deadlines,

### **Architecture Internship:**

02/2018-03/2019

 Worked alongside 2 other interns and a junior Architect in developing, desining and drawing architectural and interiors plans and execution schemes for more than 20 projects, including a School in partnership with a architectural firm from São Paulo, designing and drawing plans for execution.

#### **Education:**

UniAcademia (former Center of Higher-Education of Juiz de Fora - CESJF):

Bachelor's Degree in Architecture and Urbanism

06/15 - 09/20 GPA 3,28/4

#### **Alura Courses:**

04/23 - present

Technical courses in programming languages and tools; python, python OOP, python for Data Science, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, React, NextJs.

Certificates